<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Etiquetas>
	<Idioma id="en">
		<LB_TituloHeader>Invoicing</LB_TituloHeader>
		<LB_Titulo>Invoicing Main Menu</LB_Titulo>
		<LB_RegistroTransacciones>Transaction Register</LB_RegistroTransacciones>
		<MSG_RegistroTransacciones>The recording transactions process includes at first instance the petty cash opening to the assigned user. One user can have more than one petty cash available, but only can open one at a time. The system displays a message if the petty cash selected is being used by another user. The user has to select the petty cash to work the invoicing.</MSG_RegistroTransacciones>
		
		<LB_CierreCajaUsuario>Cash closing by user</LB_CierreCajaUsuario>
		<MSG_CierreCajaUsuario>Allows each user enter the amounts by currency recorded during the day. Users have to relate the following datas: Initial amount and exchange rate.In cash documents have to register: total of cash income received and at front  break it down into: cash, ba</MSG_CierreCajaUsuario>
		<LB_CierreCajaSupervisor>Cash closing by supervisor</LB_CierreCajaSupervisor>
		<MSG_CierreCajaSupervisor>This option can be used only for the supervisor defined in the System Administration module.  The report allows the supervisor to review the differences against the records done by the users. Displays cash and credit transactions, and summary in local currency. The report can be generated by petty cash, displaying: petty cash number, closing date, closing hour and responsible user.</MSG_CierreCajaSupervisor>
		<LB_ImpresionFacturas>Printing Invoice</LB_ImpresionFacturas>
		<MSG_ImpresionFacturas>Allows print  posted and applied invoices, and keep track of printed invoices.  The system displays a preview and generates the print in PDF format</MSG_ImpresionFacturas>
		<LB_ReimpresionFacturas>Reprint Invoice</LB_ReimpresionFacturas>
		<MSG_ReimpresionFacturas>Allows reprint invoices already generated. The system displays a preview and generates the print in PDF format.</MSG_ReimpresionFacturas>
		<LB_PuntoVenta>Point of Sale</LB_PuntoVenta>
		<MSG_PuntoVenta>Displays an interactive report by category and allows to compare items features contained in the same category. Once selected the items, the invoice can be generated.</MSG_PuntoVenta>
		<LB_RevisionCredito>Credit Review</LB_RevisionCredito>
		<MSG_RevisionCredito>This process allows the customer to verify the available based on credit analysis performed, in order to increase the customer credit or reject the customer credit.</MSG_RevisionCredito>
		<LB_RecibirPago>Receive Payment</LB_RecibirPago>
		<MSG_RecibirPago>Displays outstanding payments from customers, using the following filters: client identify, name, amount outstanding and premium received. After selecting the payment, the full or partial amount of payment is received.</MSG_RecibirPago>
		<LB_RecibirPreFacturas>Receive Pre invoice</LB_RecibirPreFacturas>
		<MSG_RecibirPreFacturas>Allows capture sales transactions for which even do not have a definitive document  accounts receivable, allows to group more than one pre-invoice in a single document of receivables and apply pre-invoice as an estimates in the accounts receivable module.</MSG_RecibirPreFacturas>
		<LB_ImpresionDocumentos>Printing Documents</LB_ImpresionDocumentos>
		<MSG_ImpresionDocumentos>Allows print documents generated by pre-invoices applied, after printing the document the result can be register. In case of a successful print the corresponding document is created in the Accounts Receivable module and in case of failures the document ca</MSG_ImpresionDocumentos>
		<LB_CancelacionDocumentos>Cancellation of Documents</LB_CancelacionDocumentos>
		<MSG_CancelacionDocumentos>Enables to cancel documents generated by the application and printing pre-invoices. After canceling the document, pre-invoices are reactivated and can be applied again from the Pre-invoices Register option.</MSG_CancelacionDocumentos>
		<LB_FacturasImpresas>Printed Invoices</LB_FacturasImpresas>
		<MSG_FacturasImpresas>This process allows the printing of documents previously generated by the application and printed documents from this module.</MSG_FacturasImpresas>
	</Idioma>
</Etiquetas>
