<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Etiquetas><Idioma id="en"><LB_Lista_Funcionarios_Cesados>List of Officials Ceased</LB_Lista_Funcionarios_Cesados><LB_Otros_Ingresos>Other Incomes</LB_Otros_Ingresos><LB_Provisiones>Provisions</LB_Provisiones><LB_Deducciones>Deductions</LB_Deducciones><LB_Aprobacion>Aprobation</LB_Aprobacion><BTN_Fecha_de_Liquidacion>Liquidation Date</BTN_Fecha_de_Liquidacion><LB_Proceso_de_Liquidacion>Liquidation Process</LB_Proceso_de_Liquidacion><AYUDA_Proceso>Select the official ceased to make up the Liquidation.  This will carry it to the Step 1.</AYUDA_Proceso><LB_Liquidando>Liquidating</LB_Liquidando><InformacionDelEmpleado>Employee Information</InformacionDelEmpleado><LB_Fecha_de_Accion>Action Date</LB_Fecha_de_Accion><LB_Cantidad_Horas>Quantity Hours</LB_Cantidad_Horas><LB_Cantidad_Dias>Quantity Days</LB_Cantidad_Dias><LB_Importe>Value</LB_Importe><AYUDA_Otros_Ingresos>Here other additional areas of type value are registered, that will be associates to the liquidation. Once they registered these areas, select the Following button.  This will carry you out to the Step 2.</AYUDA_Otros_Ingresos><AYUDA_Provisiones>Here the concepts of provisions are registered to be cancel.A clear example of this is the contribute management that offers the business and it is given to the association so that this be who handle this contribute.  Once they registered these areas, sel</AYUDA_Provisiones><LB_Referencia>Reference</LB_Referencia><AYUDA_Deducciones>This step consists of registering those concepts that the official compromised to cancel during its stay inside the institution.  These concepts do not be able lowers of the liquidation according to what stipulates the law, is informative for treasury.  O</AYUDA_Deducciones><LB_Aportes_Realizados>Contribute Accomplished</LB_Aportes_Realizados><AYUDA_Aprobacion>This approval consists of a final verification of each one of the areas and to give for finalized the areas incomes process to the liquidation.  Once they verified these deductions, select the button to Approve.</AYUDA_Aprobacion><LB_Pasos>Steps</LB_Pasos><LB_Ayuda>Help</LB_Ayuda></Idioma></Etiquetas>
